thedeadbolt.com 2013-04-05

# Privacy Policy

To publicly display our strict policy and firm commitment regarding privacy, TheDeadbolt.com has created a statement that discloses the following information with regard to protecting your privacy, information gathering, and dissemination practices of TheDeadbolt.com.

IP Logging:  
Individual IP addresses are automatically logged at the time of visit. We use your IP addresses to execute and administer the website. Should an issue ever arise regarding the identification of a user AFTER a problem occurs, IP addresses are only used to correct or solve the problem. We do not use IP addresses for any other means beyond problem solving except for statistical analysis.

Third Party Visitor Statistics:

TheDeadbolt.com uses Google Analytics to analyze visitor behavior and daily, weekly, and yearly traffic trends. Statistics collected include browser type, OS, country, host IP, visit length, and screen resolution. No effort is made to identify individuals without their knowledge, and information is only collected for statistical purposes only.

Third Party Cookies:  
During the process of statistical analysis, Google Analytics, sends a cookie to your computer. This information is collected solely to improve the services of TheDeadbolt.com and for statistical purposes.

Advertising:

TheDeadbolt.com may serve advertisements to this site or work with a third party to serve the advertisements. Advertisements placed on the TheDeadbolt.com website may include but are not limited to banner ads, paid links, pop-up windows, pop-under windows, buttons, and sponsorships.

Users of TheDeadbolt.com and readers of TheDeadbolt.com agree that TheDeadbolt.com has the right to run such advertisements and promotions. Your correspondence or business dealing with, or participation in promotions of, advertisers found on or through the Services, including payment and delivery of related goods or services, and any other representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and such advertiser. You agree that TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings or as the result of the presence of such advertisers on the Services.

The Deadbolt has a third-party advertising account and relationship with Google and its AdSense program. At any time TheDeadbolt.com has the right to temporarily suspend its participation in the Google Adsense program in which you may or may not see Google Adsense ads on the site. By visiting TheDeadbolt.com, and any pages within TheDeadbolt.com containing Google AdSense advertising, you agree to, accept, and understand the following:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TheDeadbolt.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of TheDeadbolt.com based on their visit to TheDeadbolt.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users of TheDeadbolt.com may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
ZEDO is a 3rd party ad serving system that TheDeadbolt.com uses to deliver ads. You agree to, accept, and understand that ZEDO, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TheDeadbolt.com and that ZEDO’s use of cookies enables it to serve ads to users and readers of TheDeadbolt.com and other websites on the internet. In accordance with ZEDO’s Privacy Policy, you agree to, accept, and understand that ZEDO uses cookies to enhance the Web experience by preventing users from seeing the same Internet ad over and over again. ZEDO does not use cookies to personally identify you in any way, and these cookies cannot damage your system or files. You can tell your browser to accept or reject cookies for all sites, or for specific sites; but remember, rejecting cookies may affect the way your favorite sites behave.

You agree to and accept that TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible for the security settings and/or privacy settings of any computer or device of any user or reader of TheDeadbolt.com, and you agree to and accept that The Deadbolt.com shall not be liable for any unwanted or unexpected behavior, which includes but is not limited to any initiated downloads to the user’s computer of any kind, from ZEDO ads on TheDeadbolt.com. You agree to and accept that TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible in any way for loss, damage, support of any sort incurred as the result of the presence of ZEDO’s 3rd party ad serving system and delivery of ads to TheDeadbolt.com or any advertisers on the Services.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by ZEDO, and to know the ZEDO Privacy Policy, click here for information on the ZEDO Opt Out and here for the ZEDO Privacy Policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Personal Information:

TheDeadbolt.com does not gather, store, or collect personal contact information. Personal contact information sent from a visitor of TheDeadbolt.com to TheDeadbolt.com, whether by e-mail, written letter, verbal communication, or any other method of communication, will not be disclosed to any other third party. The visitor’s contact information may be used to respond to that particular visitor after a question, comment, or request, and may be used to contact the visitor when necessary.

At any time, in relation to contacting TheDeadbolt.com, visitors may choose to stop any and all correspondence with TheDeadbolt.com. At all times, TheDeadbolt.com gives readers the opportunity to stop receiving any and all correspondence or communication with TheDeadbolt.com.

Social Media and Social Networking

TheDeadbolt.com may or may not, at any time, utilize and incorporate various social networking platforms, applications, code, and other social networking technology for the purposes of marketing TheDeadbolt.com to a wider audience and positively engaging with our readers, which includes but is not limited to Facebook, Twitter, and similar networks.

You agree to and accept that TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible for the security settings and/or privacy policy and settings of any third party social networking company, netwrok, or website or any user or reader of TheDeadbolt.com who engages in social networking activity on or via TheDeadbolt.com, and you agree to and accept that The Deadbolt.com shall not be liable for any activity whatsoever, of any form, on any social networking website, third party application, or third party code or third party behavior a user may or may not encounter on TheDeadbolt.com, which includes but is not limited to any initiated downloads to the user’s computer of any kind or anything viewed or encountered on any third party social networking network, company, or website. You agree to and accept that TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible in any way for loss, damage, support of any sort incurred as the result of the presence of social networking applications and or code from such networks as Facebook and Twitter and delivery to TheDeadbolt.com or any user or advertiser on the Services.

You agree to and accept that any advertiser or affiliate of TheDeadbolt.com shall not be responsible or liable in any form, for any reason, for the security settings and/or privacy policy and settings of any third party social networking company or any user or reader of TheDeadbolt.com who engages in social networking activity on or via TheDeadbolt.com.

TheDeadbolt.com takes personal privacy and confidentiality of information very seriously and we urge all users of TheDeadbolt.com to check the privacy policies of all social networks before engaging in social network activity and not give out their personal information or allow it to be available without serious thought or consideration aftr reading the relevant privacy policy.

For more information, please visit http://www.facebook.com/policy.php and http://twitter.com/privacy.

Contests/Giveaways

Eligibility/Availability

Contests and giveaways on TheDeadbolt.com are void where prohibited by applicable law. The sweepstakes is open and offered only to legal residents of the United States age 13 or older. Residents of Canada and other countries are eligible to enter ONLY when specified on the contest page (void in Quebec). Winners may be required to sign an affidavit of eligibility as a condition to the delivery of the applicable prize. Employees and their immediate families/household members of TheDeadBolt.com and their respective parent companies, affiliates, and subsidiaries are not eligible to enter the contests and giveaways.

Entries/Entrants

No purchase necessary. To enter, submit all required information as specified on the contest page for a giveaway. When contacted by TheDeadbolt.com, all entrants must include the entrant’s name, age, a valid email address and shipping address if required (no P.O. Boxes) for any potential prize shipments. The first and last name provided by online entrants will be the identity of the entrant and, if selected for a prize, the identity of the winner. We reserve the right to disqualify any entries that we believe in good faith has been generated by a so-called spam or automated e-mail program or via scripts and automated submission. By participating, all entrants agree to abide by these rules.

Prizes

Prizes are specified on the contest or give-away page. Entries and prizes are nontransferable. No substitutions are permitted, except that sponsor reserves the right to substitute a prize of equal or greater monetary value for the grand prize. Winners shall be responsible and liable for any federal, state, and local taxes on the value of their prize.  
Drawing and Selection

A random drawing will take place within one month of the end of the sweepstakes or otherwise specified. The number of eligible entrants will determine odds of winning. In the event of a dispute regarding the identity of the person submitting the entry, the entry will be deemed to be submitted by the person in whose name the email account is registered. The decisions of TheDeadbolt.com are final and binding in all matters relating to this contest/giveaway. Winner will be notified by means determined by TheDeadBolt.com or its affiliated contest host, which could include by telephone, e-mail, or through social media networks such as Facebook or Twitter. If a winner is found to be ineligible, an alternate winner may be also be selected from the pool of eligible entries. There is a limit of one entry per person per email address. Duplicate entries will be void. All entries directly submitted through the website contact forms or e-mail become the property of TheDeadbolt.com and will not be returned. Enteries submitted through social networks like Facebook or Twitter become the property of that particular social network.  
General Conditions and Warranties

An entrant or winner may be disqualified from the sweepstakes if he or she fails to comply with each provision of these official rules, as determined at the discretion of TheDeadbolt.com.

TheDeadBolt.com shall not be liable for: 1. Failed, returned, or misdirected notifications based on inaccurate information provided by the winner on the sweepstakes entry form, 2. Entries, and responses to winner notifications that are lost, late, incomplete, illegible, unintelligible, postage-due, misdirected, damaged, or otherwise not received by the intended recipient in whole or in part or for computer or technical error of any kind, 3. Any electronic miscommunications or failures, technical hardware or software failures of any kind, lost or unavailable network connections, or failed, incomplete or delayed computer transmissions which may limit an entrant’s ability to participate in the sweepstakes, 4. Any technical malfunctions of the telephone network, computer online system, computer equipment, software, program malfunctions, or other failures, delayed computer transactions, or network connections that are human, mechanical, or technical in nature, or any combination thereof, including any injury or damage to entrant’s or any other person’s computer related to or resulting from downloading any part of this sweepstakes or 5. Any warranty of fitness or merchantability of any prize or the function or operation thereof, which shall be the sole responsibility of the manufacturer of the prize.

Unless prohibited by applicable law, entry constitutes permission to use an entrant’s name, address (city and state) and testimonials in all media, in perpetuity, in any manner TheDeadBolt.com deems appropriate for publicity purposes without any further compensation to such entrant.

By entering or accepting a prize in the contests/giveaways, winners agree to be bound by these official contest rules and to conform to all federal, state, and local laws and regulations and any similar or relevant international laws when contests are open to other countries. When applicable, the winner will be required to execute and return to TheDeadbolt.com within five business days an affidavit of eligibility and a liability and publicity release to be eligible for the prize or an alternate winner will be selected. Winner may be required to furnish proof of identity, address, and birth date in order to receive prize. By entering, an entrant agrees to release and hold harmless TheDeadBolt.com the artist, and their parent, subsidiary, and affiliated entities, directors, officers, employees, attorneys, agents, and representatives from any damage, injury, death, loss, claim, action, demand, or other liability (collectively claims) that may arise from their acceptance, possession and/or use of any prize in their participation in this promotion, or from any misuse or malfunction of any prize awarded, regardless of whether such claims, or knowledge of the facts constituting such claims, exist at the time of entry or arise at any time thereafter. Any person attempting to defraud or in any way tamper with this sweepstakes will be ineligible for prizes and may be prosecuted to the full extent of the law. TheDeadbolt.com reserves the right to modify the rules of the sweepstakes in any way or at any time. TheDeadBolt.com reserves the right, in their sole discretion, to cancel or suspend this sweepstakes should viruses, bugs, or other causes beyond their control corrupt the administration, security, or proper play of the contests.

External Linking:

TheDeadbolt.com contains external links to other websites. TheDeadbolt.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other website.

Security:

Security measures are in place and in effect at TheDeadbolt.com to ensure the protection of all data and the possible incorrect or inappropriate use, modification, or loss of any content on the website. TheDeadbolt.com takes every precaution to ensure that all personal information is properly protected and is kept secure against misuse, improper modification, or loss. All personal information that is collected and stored on TheDeadbolt.com’s servers is deemed confidential and is not made available to the public. Access to all personal information is password protected.

Liability and Limitation:

You agree that you are visiting TheDeadbolt.com of your own volition and you will not hold TheDeadbolt.com, or any other entity governed by or directly affiliated with TheDeadbolt.com, liable for any damages or issues on the “user end” that might arise out of visiting TheDeadbolt.com.

Notification of Changes:

TheDeadbolt.com reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time. In the event that we change or modify our Privacy Policy, all changes will be posted on this page, and will take effect 7 days after the posting, so that the user is aware of our information gathering, storing and disseminating practices. All information that has been changed will be used in accordance with the privacy policy under which it was collected.

Contacting the Web Site:

If you have any questions or any concerns regarding this privacy policy, the practices of TheDeadbolt.com, or your interaction with this website, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at info@thedeadbolt.com.

You can also contact us by mail at the following address:

The Deadbolt  
901-1865 Barclay Street  
Vancouver, BC.  
V6G 1K7
